Good morning. Let's have a little chat at the beginning of the day.
Did you sleep well last night?
Did you eat breakfast?
Is that so? I'm going to eat a pancake from now on.
How's the weather now?
I see. As you can see, the weather is good here.
How have you been studying Japanese lately?
What kind of apps do you use to study Japanese?
Is there any word you've learned recently?
It's amazing that you know such a word.
By the way, what day was it today?
What are you going to do today?
Is that so? I'm going to brush my teeth after I eat breakfast and go to the post office.
By the way, what time is it now?
Is it that time already?
A fun time passes in an instant.
I hope today will be a wonderful day.
See you later.
Good morning. Let's have a little chat at the beginning of the day.
Did you sleep well last night?
Yes, I slept well.
Did you eat breakfast?
Yes, I ate bread and apples.
Is that so? I'm going to eat a pancake from now on.
How's the weather now?
It's raining a little.
That's right.
As you can see here, the weather is good.
How have you been studying Japanese lately?
I study for an hour every day, but it's difficult to remember words.
What kind of apps do you use to study Japanese?
I use YouTube or Netflix to study.
What words have you learned recently?
I learned the word eat-all yesterday.
It's amazing that you know such a word.
By the way, what day was it today?
It's Saturday, February 25th.
What are you going to do today?
I'm going to do homework at school and go to the supermarket with my mother.
Is that so? I'm going to wash the dishes, brush my teeth, and go to the post office after I eat breakfast.
By the way, what time is it now?
It's 820 minutes.
Is it that time already?
A fun time passes in a flash.
I hope you have a wonderful day today.
See you later.